<resources>
    <string name="app_name">alpha</string>

    <string name="bottom_nav_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_account">Account</string>

    <!--strings for GRE Activity-->
    <string name="gre_overview">The Graduate Record Examinations, often known as GRE, are conducted by Educational Testing Services (ETS). Broadly categorised, there are two types of GRE - GRE General Test and GRE Subject Tests. The GRE tests are one of the most widely accepted tests across the world.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_learn_more"><u>Learn more about the GRE General Test</u></string>
    <string name="gre_subject_learn_more"><u>Learn more about the GRE Subject Tests</u></string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Exam Pattern Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_sections_overview">The GRE General Test is a widely accepted test for masters, doctorate and other specialised programs. The test consists of three types of sections.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_awa_title">Analytical Writing Assessment (AWA)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_awa_overview">This section type tests your thinking and analytical skills by requiring you write you an essay based on the instructions provided.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_awa_learn_more"><u>Learn more about AWA-Measure</u></string>

    <string name="gre_general_verbal_title">Verbal Reasoning (V)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_overview">This section type tests your ability to understand the text, analyse and draw conclusions by requiring you to solve various types of Verbal Reasoning questions.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_learn_more"><u>Learn more about V-Measure</u></string>

    <string name="gre_general_quant_title">Quantitative Reasoning (Q)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_overview">This section type tests your ability to interpret and analyse quantitative information by requiring you to solve various types of Quantitative Reasoning questions.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_learn_more"><u>Learn more about Q-Measure</u></string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Modes Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_modes_overview">The GRE General Test is available in two modes - computer-delivered and paper-delivered.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_title">Computer-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_overview">The computer-delivered test requires you have prerequisite knowledge about operating a basic computer in the testing environment. It comes with additional features compared to the paper-delivered test.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_learn_more"><u>Learn more about computer-delivered test</u></string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_title">Paper-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_overview">The paper-delivered test does not require you to have any prerequisite knowledge, but has its own limitations compared to the computer-delivered test.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_learn_more"><u>Learn more about paper-delivered test</u></string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Computer Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_computer_sections_title">Sections</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_sections_details">You are required to attempt a total of 6 sections:\n\n - 1 AWA-Measure section (1 hr)\n - 2 V-Measure sections (30 min each)\n - 2 Q-Measure sections (35 min each)\n - 1 Experimental section (30 min or 35 min)</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_order_title">Order</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_order_details">The order of sections in the test is:\n\n1. AWA-Measure\n2. V-Measure 1 or Q-Measure 1\n3. Q-Measure 1 or V-Measure 1\n --- 10 min break --- \n4. V-Measure 2 or Q-Measure 2\n5. Q-Measure 2 or V-Measure 2\n6. V-Measure 3 or Q-Measure 3</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_unidentified_title">Experimental Section</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_unidentified_details"> - The experimental section can be a V-Measure section or a Q-Measure section.\n\n - It can appear anywhere in the test after the AWA section.\n\n - There is no way to determine whether a section in the test is experimental. For example, if you get 3 V-Measure sections and 2 Q-Measure sections in the test, it can be inferred that one of those V-Measure sections was experimental. However, there is absolutely no way to determine which one of those sections was experimental.\n\n - The experimental section does not count towards your ultimate score.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_break_title">Breaks</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_break_details"> - You get a 1 min break after the end of each section. You are not allowed to leave your desk during this break.\n\n - After the end of the third section, you get a 10 min break. You are allowed to leave your desk during this break.\n\n - All the breaks are optional. One may chose to skip any of the breaks.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_time_title">Total Time</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_time_details">The total duration of the computer-delivered test is around 4 hours, depending upon the combination of sections that you get on the test.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_features_title">Features</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_features_details">The computer-delivered test provides the following features:\n\n - You can skip a question within a section. However, you cannot skip a section. You have to submit and end a section to proceed with another section.\n\n - You can change or edit your answer for a question at any point of time within a section.\n\n - You can mark a question and review it later at any point of time within a section.\n\n - You can get overall preview of the section at any point of time within a section.\n\n - On-screen calculator is available for Q-Measure sections.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Paper Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_paper_details"></string>

</resources>
