<resources>
    <string name="app_name">alpha</string>

    <string name="bottom_nav_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_account">Account</string>

    <!--strings for GRE Activity-->
    <string name="gre_overview">The Graduate Record Examinations, often known as GRE, are conducted by Educational Testing Services (ETS). Broadly categorised, there are two types of GRE - GRE General Test and GRE Subject Tests. The GRE tests are one of the most widely accepted tests across the world.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_learn_more"><u>Learn more about the GRE General Test</u></string>
    <string name="gre_subject_learn_more"><u>Learn more about the GRE Subject Tests</u></string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Exam Pattern Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_sections_overview">The GRE General Test is a widely accepted test for masters, doctorate and other specialised programs. The test consists of three types of sections.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_awa_title">Analytical Writing Assessment (AWA)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_awa_overview">This section type tests your thinking and analytical skills by requiring you write you an essay based on the instructions provided.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_awa_learn_more"><u>Learn more about AWA-Measure</u></string>

    <string name="gre_general_verbal_title">Verbal Reasoning (V)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_overview">This section type tests your ability to understand the text, analyse and draw conclusions by requiring you to solve various types of Verbal Reasoning questions.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_learn_more"><u>Learn more about V-Measure</u></string>

    <string name="gre_general_quant_title">Quantitative Reasoning (Q)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_overview">This section type tests your ability to interpret and analyse quantitative information by requiring you to solve various types of Quantitative Reasoning questions.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_learn_more"><u>Learn more about Q-Measure</u></string>

    <!--strings for GRE General AWA Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_awa_details"> - The GRE General Test consists of exactly 1 AWA section.\n\n - The AWA section consists of two essay writing tasks, half an hour each.\n\n - The AWA section always appears at the beginning of the GRE General Test.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_awa_issue_title">Issue Task</string>
    <string name="gre_general_awa_issue_details"> - The Issue Task requires you to write an essay by analysing the given issue.\n\n - You are required to take up a side by agreeing, disagreeing or being neutral, and put forward your points in a logical fashion.\n\n - The task assess your ability to think critically around a given topic and express your thoughts clearly.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_awa_argument_title">Argument Task</string>
    <string name="gre_general_awa_argument_details"> - The Argument Task requires you to write an essay by analysing the given argument.\n\n - You are required to note the weakness of the argument, and base your essay on the underlying assumptions of the given argument.\n\n - The task assess your ability to understand, analyse and evaluate arguments in a coherent manner.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Verbal Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_details"> - The computer-delivered test consists of 2 V-Measure sections (and 3 sections, if the experimental section is a V-Measure) of 30 min each, consisting of 20 questions.\n\n - The paper-delivered test consists of exactly 2 V-Measure sections of 35 min each, consisting of 25 questions.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_verbal_text_completion_title">Text Completion</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_text_completion_details"> - This question type requires you to complete the blanks of a given sentence or paragraphs from the available answer choices.\n\n - There can be one blank, two blanks or even three blanks in the question.\n\n - There is no partial marking. Your answer for all of the blanks must be correct.\n\n - Each blank has exactly one correct answer among the given answer choices.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_verbal_reading_comprehension_title">Reading Comprehension</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_reading_comprehension_details"> - This question type requires you to answer the question based on a comprehension passage.\n\n - The passage may be short, medium or long in terms of length.\n\n - The kind of questions based on the passage include drawing inference, analysing assumptions, identifying the meaning of words, identifying cause and result, etc.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_verbal_sentence_equivalence_title">Sentence Equivalence</string>
    <string name="gre_general_verbal_sentence_equivalence_details"> - This question type requires you to select exactly two answer choices that are similar in meaning and produce sentences with same overall meaning when filled in the blank.\n\n - There is exactly one blank and exactly two correct answer choices among the six given answer choices.\n\n - There is no partial marking. You must select both the correct answer choices.\n\n - In general, it is observed that out of the six answer choices, two of them are synonymous (and are correct), the other two of them are also synonymous (and are incorrect), and the remaining two are not synonymous.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Quant Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_quant_details"> - The computer-delivered test consists of 2 Q-Measure sections (and 3 sections, if the experimental section is a Q-Measure) of 35 min each, consisting of 20 questions.\n\n - The paper-delivered test consists of exactly 2 V-Measure sections of 40 min each, consisting of 25 questions.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_quant_comparison_title">Quantitative Comparison</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_comparison_details"> - This question type requires you to compare two mathematical quantities, A and B, and select the appropriate answer.\n\n - There are exactly four answer choices: first answer choice indicates that quantity A is greater than B, second indicates that quantity B is greater than A, third indicates that both the quantities are equal, and the fourth answer choice indicates that the relationship between them cannot be determined.\n\n - Exactly one of these answers choices is a correct answer.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_quant_mcq_single_title">MCQ (Single Answer Correct)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_mcq_single_details"> - As the title suggests, this question type is a multiple choice question with exactly one correct answer among the 5 given answer choices.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_quant_mcq_multiple_title">MCQ (Multiple Answers Correct)</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_mcq_multiple_details"> - As the title suggests, this question type is a multiple choice question with multiple correct answer choices.\n\n - The number of given answer choices may vary from question to question.\n\n - The question may or may not specify the number of correct answer choices.\n\n - There is no partial marking. You must select the exact correct answer choices to get the credit.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_quant_numeric_entry_title">Numeric Entry</string>
    <string name="gre_general_quant_numeric_entry_details"> - This question type requires you to provide answer in the form of an integer or a decimal in a single answer box, or as a fraction in two answer boxes (one for numerator and the other for denominator).\n\n - The question always states the format in which the answer is expected, including the number of digits required after the decimal point.\n\n - In case of fractions, always reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Modes Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_modes_overview">The GRE General Test is available in two modes - computer-delivered and paper-delivered.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_title">Computer-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_overview">The computer-delivered test requires you have prerequisite knowledge about operating a basic computer in the testing environment. It comes with additional features compared to the paper-delivered test.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_learn_more"><u>Learn more about computer-delivered test</u></string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_title">Paper-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_overview">The paper-delivered test does not require you to have any prerequisite knowledge, but has its own limitations compared to the computer-delivered test.</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_learn_more"><u>Learn more about paper-delivered test</u></string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Computer Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_computer_sections_title">Sections</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_sections_details">You are required to attempt a total of 6 sections:\n\n - 1 AWA-Measure section (1 hr)\n - 2 V-Measure sections (30 min each)\n - 2 Q-Measure sections (35 min each)\n - 1 Experimental section (30 min or 35 min)</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_order_title">Order</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_order_details">The order of sections in the test is:\n\n1. AWA-Measure\n2. V-Measure 1 or Q-Measure 1\n3. Q-Measure 1 or V-Measure 1\n --- 10 min break --- \n4. V-Measure 2 or Q-Measure 2\n5. Q-Measure 2 or V-Measure 2\n6. V-Measure 3 or Q-Measure 3</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_unidentified_title">Experimental Section</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_unidentified_details"> - The experimental section can be a V-Measure section or a Q-Measure section.\n\n - It can appear anywhere in the test after the AWA section.\n\n - There is no way to determine whether a section in the test is experimental. For example, if you get 3 V-Measure sections and 2 Q-Measure sections in the test, it can be inferred that one of those V-Measure sections was experimental. However, there is absolutely no way to determine which one of those sections was experimental.\n\n - The experimental section does not count towards your ultimate score.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_break_title">Breaks</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_break_details"> - You get a 1 min break after the end of each section. You are not allowed to leave your desk during this break.\n\n - After the end of the third section, you get a 10 min break. You are allowed to leave your desk during this break.\n\n - All the breaks are optional. One may chose to skip any of the breaks.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_time_title">Total Time</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_time_details">The total duration of the computer-delivered test is around 4 hours, depending upon the combination of sections that you get on the test.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_computer_features_title">Features</string>
    <string name="gre_general_computer_features_details">The computer-delivered test provides the following features:\n\n - You can skip a question within a section. However, you cannot skip a section. You have to submit and end a section to proceed with another section.\n\n - You can change or edit your answer for a question at any point of time within a section.\n\n - You can mark a question and review it later at any point of time within a section.\n\n - You can get overall preview of the section at any point of time within a section.\n\n - On-screen calculator is available for Q-Measure sections.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Paper Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_paper_sections_title">Sections</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_sections_details">You are required to attempt a total of 5 sections:\n\n - 1 AWA-Measure section (1 hr)\n - 2 V-Measure sections (35 min each)\n - 2 Q-Measure sections (40 min each)</string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_order_title">Order</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_order_details">The order of sections in the test is:\n\n1. AWA-Measure\n2. V-Measure 1 or Q-Measure 1\n --- 10 min break --- \n3. Q-Measure 1 or V-Measure 1\n4. V-Measure 2 or Q-Measure 2\n5. Q-Measure 2 or V-Measure 2</string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_unidentified_title">Experimental Section</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_unidentified_details"> - The paper-delivered test does not come with an experimental section.\n\n - All the sections in the test contribute towards your ultimate score.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_break_title">Breaks</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_break_details"> - You get a 1 min break after the end of each section. You are not allowed to leave your desk during this break.\n\n - After the end of the second section, you get a 10 min break. You are allowed to leave your desk during this break.\n\n - All the breaks are optional. One may chose to skip any of the breaks.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_time_title">Total Time</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_time_details">The total duration of the paper-delivered test is around 3 hrs 30 min.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_paper_features_title">Features</string>
    <string name="gre_general_paper_features_details">The paper-delivered test provides the following features:\n\n - Answers are to be entered directly in the test book. You are not required to write answers on a separate answer sheet.\n\n - You will be provided with a calculator for Q-Measure sections. You are not allowed to use your own calculator.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Scoring Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_score_scales_title">Score Scales</string>
    <string name="gre_general_score_scales_details"> - The Verbal Reasoning score is reported on a scale of 130 to 170, in 1 point increments.\n\n - The Quantitative Reasoning score is reported on a scale of 130 to 170, in 1 point increments.\n\n - The Analytical Writing Assessment is reported on a scale of 0 to 6, in half (0.5) point increments.\n\n - Any section with all unattempted questions is reported as No Score (NS).</string>

    <string name="gre_general_score_computer_title">Computer-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_score_computer_details"> - All operational sections (apart from the Experimental Section) contribute towards the total score.\n\n - For V-Measure and Q-Measure, a raw score is computed. The raw score is the number of questions answered correctly. Within each section, all questions contribute equally to the total score. The raw score is then converted to a scaled score through a process called equating, which accounts for the minor variations in the toughness levels across sections as well as test dates.\n\n - For AWA-Measure, each essay receives a score from one human moderator and a score from one computer program called e-rater. If the both these scores closely agree, the ultimate score is their average. If not, then another score is obtained from a human moderator and the ultimate score for the essay is the average of two human scores. The overall score for AWA-Measure is the average score obtained for the two essays, rounded to nearest half-point interval on the 0 to 6 scale.\n\n - The scores are reported for V-Measure, Q-Measure and AWA-Measure separately. For example, V: 160, Q: 163, AWA: 4.5</string>

    <string name="ger_general_score_paper_title">Paper-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_score_paper_details"> - All the sections contribute towards to the total score.\n\n - For V-Measure and Q-Measure, a raw score is computed. The raw score is the number of questions answered correctly. Within each section, all questions contribute equally to the total score. The raw score is then converted to a scaled score through a process called equating, which accounts for the minor variations in the toughness levels across sections as well as test dates.\n\n - For AWA-Measure, each essay receives scores from two human moderators. If the two scores differ by more than one point on the scale, then a third human moderator clears the discrepancy. Otherwise, the ultimate score for the essay is the average of the two human scores. The overall score for AWA-Measure is the average score obtained for the two essays, rounded to nearest half-point interval on the 0 to 6 scale.\n\n - The scores are reported for V-Measure, Q-Measure and AWA-Measure separately. For example, V: 160, Q: 163, AWA: 4.5</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Score Reporting Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_score_select_title">Score Select</string>
    <string name="gre_general_score_select_details"> - You can send your test scores to up to 4 graduate institutions or fellowship sponsors. This is included in your test fee.\n\n - The Score Select option gives you the ability to decide which scores you want to send to the designated institutions.\n\n - If you want to send your scores to additional institutions or decide to send them after the test day, additional score reports can be sent at 27 USD per recipient.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_score_reporting_computer_title">Computer-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_score_reporting_computer_details"> - On the test day itself, after completing your test, you can view your informal V-Measure and Q-Measure scores.\n\n - You can use the Score Select option to send the most recent scores or all the scores to up to 4 recipients.\n\n - You can also choose to not send any scores at that time, but you cannot use the opportunity to send the scores to 4 recipients for free, later.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_score_reporting_paper_title">Paper-delivered Test</string>
    <string name="gre_general_score_reporting_paper_details"> - You have to mention the 4 recipients when you register for the test.\n\n - During the registration process itself, you will have to choose whether you want to send the most recent scores or all the scores.\n\n - You can also choose to not mention any recipients during registration, but you cannot use the opportunity to send the scores to 4 recipients for free, later.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_validity_title">Validity</string>
    <string name="gre_general_validity_details">The scores of GRE General Test are valid and reportable for 5 years, from your test day.</string>

    <string name="gre_general_official_report_title">Formal Score Report</string>
    <string name="gre_general_official_report_details"> - Your score report indicates your designated recipients and your cumulative record reported at that time.\n\n - The score report is intended only for information and personal record.\n\n - The Graduate Institution Score Report, which is received by your recipients, includes your name, address, email, phone number, intended graduate major, GRE test scores and associated percentile ranks. It does not include any information concerning other recipients or the scores you have chosen not to report.</string>

    <!--strings for GRE General Adaptive Activity-->
    <string name="gre_general_adaptive"> - This is applicable only for the computer-delivered test.\n\n - The GRE General Test (computer-delivered) is section adaptive.\n\n - This means that the level of a V-Measure or Q-Measure section that you get is dependent upon how you solve the previous V-Measure or Q-Measure section.\n\n - However, it is important to not that how you solve the questions within a section does not impact the level of remaining questions that you receive in the same section.\n\n - Each V-Measure or Q-Measure section is considered easy, medium or hard based on the composition of the section. Each test-taker begins with a medium V-Measure or Q-Measure section. For instance, if the test-taker performs really well in this section, then the next V-Measure or Q-Measure section is expected to be hard.</string>

    <!--strings for Step Buttons-->
    <string name="button_done">MARK AS DONE</string>
    <string name="button_pending">MARK AS PENDING</string>

    <!--strings for Step1 Activity-->
    <string name="step1_intro">To begin with, you must know what you want to do. You must have a clear idea about what you have done till now, in terms of your education, work experience, likes and dislikes. You cannot simply go ahead and pursue a random academic program by shelling out a sum of money.</string>

    <string name="step1_heading1">Do what you love</string>
    <string name="step1_body1">Well, this might be one of the most hackneyed thought that you have heard. As familiar as it gets, this little phrase speaks out the best advice. And this is probably the ideal time to decide what you love.\n\nYou cannot simply pursue further education in the area you have been working relentlessly just because you landed up there. If you pursue further education without careful deliberation over what you actually want to do, then you are very likely to end up into a trouble and eventually hating your life.\n\nIrrespective of whether you like your own area of study, it is essentially important to think about what you want to do. This might be in terms of what you love doing, or what you like studying about, or what kind of job you like - something on similar lines.</string>

    <string name="step1_heading2">Decide what you want to do</string>
    <string name="step1_body2">You might end up having multiple interests, or even mixed interests. That is absolutely okay. Channelise your thoughts deeply by looking at each of these interests to arrive at one. If not, try to end up with up to two interests, which are mostly similar. The crux here is that you need to know and be completely clear about what you want to do, before proceeding with anything else. A wrong decision at this stage can be extremely painful.</string>

    <string name="step1_heading3">Do not fear</string>
    <string name="step1_body3">You might feel that something you want to is very divergent from what you have doing till now. It might be a completely disparate domain of study. Do not get scared or even hesitate at this point. There is a lot more to do ahead. So, it is okay to want to do something that does not align with your current area of study or work.</string>

    <!--strings for Step2 Activity-->
    <string name="step2_intro">Once you have decided what you want to do, it is a perfect time to research. This is the most crucial step in the entire process. A thorough research into the area in which you want to go ahead gives you the ultimate call for pursuing it, and in some cases, warns you to be cautious. Now, there are a lot of things that you need to research. Let us take them one by one.</string>

    <string name="step2_heading1">Area of Study</string>
    <string name="step2_body1">It may be the case that you have an overview of the area of study you want to get in. However, it is vital to know the depth of it. You must know what the area of study is all about and what all components does it cover. Any misunderstandings or even doubts that you might have about the area of study must be cleared at this point. You must know what you are going to be dealing with.</string>

    <string name="step2_heading2">Relevant Programs</string>
    <string name="step2_body2">Once you know what exactly you are going to study, it is time to research about the universities and their programs in the corresponding area of study. You have to know what these programs provide as a part of their curriculum, what kind of learning is expected from these programs. There may be several programs from the same university or even multiple universities and each of them might have something distinct.</string>

    <string name="step2_heading3">Career Outcomes</string>
    <string name="step2_body3">This part is very fragile. You must carefully consider and look at the career outcomes of each of the programs that you have researched. You need to know what kind of careers open up for students of the particular area of study. Additionally, it is better to have an idea about that kind of work and salary does each of these job roles associates with.</string>

    <string name="step2_heading4">Future Prospects?</string>
    <string name="step2_body4">It should be noted that this part is not the same as researching about career outcomes. Researching about future prospects involves learning about what the long term picture looks like. Where can you land up in the long term if you pick this up? Even for people who might not be into industry based programs, this is a good task to do.</string>

    <string name="step2_heading5">Do not be afraid to go back</string>
    <string name="step2_body5">By this time, you should have a good knowledge about what the area of study that you are looking for is about, what you are going to study, what kind of jobs will open up and what the related professional future might look like. If you are happily willing to pursue the area of study based on your thorough research, then you are all set. On the other side, if you have researched and got your questions answered, and still feel unsure, then do not be afraid to go back and introspect. Maybe, mixed interests brought you thinking you like this area of study. Pick the right area of study and repeat.</string>

    <string name="step2_heading6">Research thoroughly</string>
    <string name="step2_body6">A thorough research is going to help you decide properly. You need to be absolutely serious as well as curious. You have got the internet, search through it. Visit trusted websites. Look for deeper content. Connect with seniors and professionals who are familiar with the area of study to gather advice. Talk on phone, chat using messengers, get connected on platforms like LinkedIn. Do all of it, because this is what will give you the information you need.</string>

</resources>
